A Finding Aid to the Morris Louis and Morris Louis Estate papers, circa 1910s-2007, bulk 1965-2000, in the Archives of American Art AAA.louimorr
Archives of American Art
- Morris Louis Estate Papers, bulk 1965-2000; 1947-2007; Series 2; 14.9 Linear feet Boxes 3-19, OV 20
  - Project Files, 1966-2007; 2.8
    - Anita Faatz Interviews, 1970-1976; 2.8.6
      - Sybil Meyersburg Interview, 1970; 1 Sound cassettes Includes transcript. (Box 17, Folder 23-24)
      - Cornelia Noland Interview, 1971; 1 Sound cassettes Includes transcript. (Box 17, Folder 25-26)
      - Kenneth Noland Interview, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 27)
        Includes transcript notes only.
      - Liz Whitney Quisgard Interview, 1970-1971; 2 Sound cassettes Includes transcript. (Box 17, Folder 28-29)
      - Lawrence Rubin and William Rubin Interviews, 1971; 1 Sound cassettes Includes transcripts. (Box 18, Folder 1-3)
      - Betty Schach and Betty Carter Interviews, 1970; 1 Sound cassettes Includes transcript (Betty Schach). (Box 18, Folder 4-5)
        For Betty Carter Interview transcript, see Box 17, Folder 9
      - Charles Schucker Interview, 1970; 1 Sound cassettes Includes transcript. (Box 18, Folder 6-7)
      - Leon Shereshefsky and Pauline Shereshefsky Interviews, 1971; 1 Sound cassettes Includes transcripts. (Box 18, Folder 8-10)
      - Annie Siegel Interview (transcript), 1970 (Box 18, Folder 11)
      - Ann Spiegel Interview, 1970; 1 Sound cassettes No transcript included. (Box 18, Folder 12)
      - I. S. Weissbrodt Interview, 1971; 1 Sound cassettes No transcript included. (Box 18, Folder 13)